export default data8 = [
    {
        id: "q1",
        question: "Which flower is associated with Northern Ireland?",
        options: ["The daffodil", "The thistle", "The shamrock", "The rose"],
        correct_option: "The shamrock"
    },
     {
        id: "q2",
        question: "The last battle between Britain and France was the battle of Waterloo.",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        correct_option: "True"
    },
     {
        id: "q3",
        question: "£100 is the highest value note in circulation in the UK.",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        correct_option: "False"
    },
     {
        id: "q4",
        question: "Where is the Lake District National Park located?",
        options: ["Scotland", "Wales", "England", "Northern Ireland"],
        correct_option: "England"
    },
     {
        id: "q5",
        question: "Who was born in Stratford-upon-Avon?",
        options: ["Jane Austen", "Charles Dickens", "William Shakespeare", "Thomas Hardy"],
        correct_option: "William Shakespeare"
    },
     {
        id: "q6",
        question: "What does Hogmanay refer to?",
        options: ["Christmas Day in Wales", "New Year's Eve in Scotland", "Christmas Day in Scotland", "New Year's Eve in Wales"],
        correct_option: "New Year's Eve in Scotland"
    },
     {
        id: "q7",
        question: "What is the capital city of Northern Ireland?",
        options: ["Cork", "Edinburgh", "Belfast", "Dublin"],
        correct_option: "Belfast"
    },
     {
        id: "q8",
        question: "Which of the following wars took place between 1899 and 1902 in South Africa?",
        options: ["The Hundred Years War", "The Boer War", "The First World War", "The Crimean War"],
        correct_option: "The Boer War"
    },
     {
        id: "q9",
        question: "Northern Ireland uses a system called ‘individual registration’ and all those entitled to vote must complete their own registration form.",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        correct_option: "True"
    },
     {
        id: "q10",
        question: "How old do citizens of the UK, the Irish Republic or the Commonwealth have to be to stand for public office?",
        options: ["18", "21", "16", "25"],
        correct_option: "18"
    },
     {
        id: "q11",
        question: "How did the Government promote policies of free trade during the Victorian Age?",
        options: ["Abolishing a number of taxes on imported goods", "Abolishing the exportation of local produce", "Preventing the importation of cheap raw materials", "Preventing the importation of cheap grain"],
        correct_option: "Abolishing a number of taxes on imported goods"
    },
     {
        id: "q12",
        question: "Which invention lead to the rapid development of the industry in Britain during the 18th and 19th centuries?",
        options: ["The Radar", "The Steam Power", "The Jet Engine", "The Turing Machine"],
        correct_option: "The Steam Power"
    },
     {
        id: "q13",
        question: "MPs can only be contacted by post.",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        correct_option: "False"
    },
     {
        id: "q14",
        question: "What movement challenged the authority of the Pope?",
        options: ["The Swinging Sixties", "The Reformation", "The Suffragettes", "The Enlightenment"],
        correct_option: "The Reformation"
    },
     {
        id: "q15",
        question: "What English King introduced the Domesday Book?",
        options: ["King Henry V", "King Henry IV", "William the Conqueror", "Harold, the Saxon king of England"],
        correct_option: "William the Conqueror"
    },
     {
        id: "q16",
        question: "What is the small claims procedure?",
        options: ["An informal way of helping people to settle minor disputes without spending a lot of time and money using a lawyer", "A procedure that helps people to make small home insurance claims in certain circumstances"],
        correct_option: "An informal way of helping people to settle minor disputes without spending a lot of time and money using a lawyer"
    },
     {
        id: "q17",
        question: "What building was constructed in Hyde Park to hold the Great Exhibition of 1851?",
        options: ["The Crystal Palace", "Buckingham Palace", "Kensington Palace", "Apsley House"],
        correct_option: "The Crystal Palace"
    },
     {
        id: "q18",
        question: "Who was Florence Nightingale?",
        options: ["An economist", "A painter", "A nurse", "A poet"],
        correct_option: "A nurse"
    },
     {
        id: "q19",
        question: "Which of the following is NOT a role of the Queen:",
        options: ["To inaugurate important business in the UK", "To entertain visiting heads of state", "To receive foreign ambassadors and high commissioners", "To make state visits overseas"],
        correct_option: "To inaugurate important business in the UK"
    },
     {
        id: "q20",
        question: "The Speaker is a neutral MP and does not represent a political party:",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        correct_option: "True"
    },
     {
        id: "q21",
        question: "What is the height of the London Eye?",
        options: ["125 metres", "135 metres", "140 metres", "152 metres"],
        correct_option: "135 metres"
    },
     {
        id: "q22",
        question: "What name is given to the celebration when people in Great Britain set off fireworks at home or in special displays on the 5th of November?",
        options: ["Bonfire night", "Fireworks night", "Bright night", "The candles night"],
        correct_option: "Bonfire night"
    },
     {
        id: "q23",
        question: "When did the Vikings first visit Britain to raid coastal towns and take away goods and slaves?",
        options: ["AD 600", "AD 789", "AD 790", "AD 804"],
        correct_option: "AD 789"
    },
     {
        id: "q24",
        question: "How many National Parks are there in England, Wales and Scotland?",
        options: ["10", "12", "15", "25"],
        correct_option: "15"
    },
    
]